{
    "id": "c8e7be34cb4945599c864ac50ce2643d",
    "title": "Adjectives Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Melvin is …………………………. Edwin.",
            "description": "Elder cannot be used predicatively (after a verb).",
            "answers": [
                "elder than",
                "elder to",
                "older than"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She is older ………………………….. her husband.",
            "description": "Use than after older.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is junior ……………………….. me.",
            "description": "The words junior and senior are followed by to.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He earns more than …………………………..",
            "description": "A subject pronoun is unusual after than.",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "I"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I prefer running ……………………….. jogging.",
            "description": "Prefer should be followed by to.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "over",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "That was ……………………….. experience in my life.",
            "description": "Worst is the superlative form of bad.",
            "answers": [
                "the worse",
                "the worst",
                "the baddest"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am older than ………………………….. is.",
            "description": "We use a subject pronoun after than when the pronoun is followed by a verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "him",
                "he"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I prefer coffee ………………………….. tea.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "to",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ………………………… than I am.",
            "description": "Worse is the comparative form of bad.",
            "answers": [
                "worse",
                "worst",
                "bad"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Humans are ……………………………. than animals.",
            "description": "The comparative form of intelligent is more intelligent. ",
            "answers": [
                "more intelligent",
                "intelligenter",
                "most intelligent"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ……………………………. of the two.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the cleverer",
                "the cleverest",
                "the clever"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My ………………………….. brother is a soldier.",
            "description": "Elder and older can both be used before nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "elder",
                "older",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}